Aah!
- Whoo!
- Ha ha ha!
Aah!
Oh, man! Heh heh.
- Did you see that?
- Woo!
Oh, my God. Ha ha!
- Yes! Yes!
- Nice, nice, nice.
- Aw, sick!
- Worth the wait.
Oh, babe. You missed out.
Yes!
I want to get off.
Whoo! Ow!
Ha ha ha!
That was intense, man.
To feel how that would be
to just crash and burn like that.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe for you,
but our lives are actually goin' somewhere.
Oh! OK, well, where we gotta go
is to the roller coaster.
'Cause our pass is for 9:15.
If we miss that,
we'll stand in line...
for, like, a day and a half,
and that's gonna kill me.
- OK!
- All right?
So let's go.
They're totally gonna dig this, man!
OK. Come on, it won't kill us to get
a deep-fried Snickers and a Coke.
Before ridin' Devil's Flight?
Yeah, that might kill me.
No! What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, man.
Ha ha ha!
- Unh!
- Ha ha!
Oh, I'll take that.
No. Come on, gimme.
It's not even mine, Kevin.
It's the yearbook's.
Just... Kevin.
Ha ha!
- Oh!
- Oh, got it.
- Oh, my God, you're such an idiot.
- Hey. Hey. Gimme the...
Ha ha!
- Ow!
- Nice.
Um, could you, like,
please delete that one of Stacy?
Ha ha!
These are for the yearbook.
And I have to turn them in tomorrow
to make a deadline...
and, like, I doubt it if a shot of
Stacy Kobayashi's camel toe...
is gonna make it in there.
Whew. I'd buy two.
Ha ha ha!
Number 38, your order's ready.
That's us.
I am so sorry.
Kevin can get so out of control.
Let me just say
he would make me crazy.
Ha! I mean, you know
I'm such a control freak...
like I couldn't handle that.
I'm breaking up with him.
Couple of weeks.
After graduation.
I've been wanting to for a while.
But don't tell anybody, OK?
Whoa. Ha ha!
Now, that shot there?
That'll sell some yearbooks.
- I love it.
Oh! Oh, all right,
so I'm a total whore.
Come on, go, go, go,
go, go, go go!
Oh, my God, Ashley, you're winning.
You're totally winning.
- Am I winning?
- Yeah, come on, hurry!
OK, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Am I winning? Look around,
I don't want to look.
You're totally winning.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
- Don't look!
- Oh, my God! Come on!
Oh, my God!
I'm winning! I'm winning!
Aah! Aah!
- I won!
- I knew you would.
Oh, my God! Gimme my prize.
- Good job.
- That was so awesome, Ashley.
Ashley.
Woo! Ha ha!
How ya doin', my brother?
You havin' a good time, huh?
- You like that?
- Ha ha!
Yeah! You like it.
Give it up. Give it up.
Whoo-ooh!
Sam!
Excuse me.
You're not a senior.
And what are
you gonna do about it...
Miss "Cutest Couple,"
Rah Rah? Ha ha!
Mom know you're here?
You are a complete bitch
if you tell her.
Proof where you were.
Take a shot of this.
Ha ha ha!
Yeah! That's what I'm talking about.
That's three.
# That is three, number three #
# Oh, I'm the man, I'm the man #
Man, I am hot.
- Man, gimme some right here, man.
- Right here! Right here!
What you doin'?
Get the fuck back. Hoo!
My God, I am good. Here we go.
Boy, I'll tell ya...
Goddamn. Whoo!
Kind sir, step right up!
There ya go. Whaddaya want?
Here we go, baby.
3 for 3. It's all mine.
Here we go. Here we go.
Big prize. Watch out.
Come on.
Unh!
Ho ho ho!
# That's what I'm talkin' 'bout #
We gonna get that one.
You want that blue one?
That's the one we gonna get.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
You can run, but you cannot hide.
- Yes!
- Whoo! Here we are, baby.
- Whoo!
- There it is.
- Awesome.
Here, get a pic of this. Ahhh!
This is the beginning of the end.
Ha ha ha!
Hey, guys, get in line.
Let's go on again!
What's wrong?
I'm...
I was having that feeling
like dejá vu, you know?
Except for something
that hasn't happened yet.
Hey, J.
Come on, man, let's go.
- Yeah, yeah, hold on.
- Come on.
What, are you weirded out
by the ride?
'Cause, look, I know you.
And I think that maybe...
you're nervous about
this roller coaster...
because they say the real fear
with these rides...
comes from the feeling
of having no control.
Everyone imagines weird stuff
when they get scared.
But it never turns out
to be what they imagine.
Never.
OK.
You can run, but you cannot hide.
Oh! Where you guys are right now
if you raise your hands and just...
Ha... cup them slightly...
it'll look you're holding
the devil's balls.
And we'd wanna do that why?
When else you ever gonna see
a dick that big?
I'm lookin' at one right now.
Ha ha!
Man, you guys are smokin' hot.
- Get out, Frankie.
- Yeah, why are you even here?
Yeah, you graduated,
like, two years ago.
I stuck around to monitor
your development.
Yeah. Good to go.
Good to go, baby.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Come on. Come on.
You may never return
from Devil's Flight.
Ha ha ha ha!
You're totally sad.
Try not to scream!
Ha ha ha!
That was totally awesome!
Yeah! Sweet!
You all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
A roller coaster
is just elemental physics.
A conversion of potential energy
to kinetic energy.
Yeah. Odds are like
one in 250 million...
of dying in a roller coaster.
Yeah, yeah,
thanks for that, McKinley.
You're more likely to die
driving to an amusement park...
than dying at one.
Whoo! Heh.
Here we go.
Whoo!
You like this?
Won it on the Wacky Ladder.
You know that ladder deal
that wobbles? Took it.
I like this. It's old school.
Frankie Cheeks
is old school, ladies.
What's that?
Oh, well, it'd be my honor.
Ew.
Oh! Let's go.
Hey... Baby.
- How many?
- Uh, 4.
- 4.
- Yeah.
Uh, gate one.
- Yeah. Front car.
- Yes!
Wait... No. No, please.
I'm sorry, I don't wanna be a hassle.
I just... I can't sit in the front.
I cannot see the tracks. I'll freak.
OK. Take it easy.
Uh, well, Carrie will sit in
the back with you. Right, babe?
Uh! Why me?
What? 'Cause we're girls?
Fuck that. I'm going to Berkeley
and I won't get to do this for a while.
I'm sitting in the front.
J, just go, OK? I'll live.
You're not gonna sit by yourself.
All right, you know what?
We'll just settle this like real men.
How about that? Hmm? Call it.
Heads.
Shit! Damn it.
All right, fine, what the fuck.
It's the same ride, right?
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
Hey, uh, just do me a favor.
Keep an eye on her, OK?
She's kinda freaked out.
- Oh. Cool.
- All right?
Yeah. Boom, buddy.
No problem.
Ha ha ha!
Aaah!
Ohh!
Here we go. Hey!
J! Keep your hands
to yourself, man.
I'm serious. You know,
payback's a bitch, OK?
You know, she might need
some comforting...
and I'll be there for her. OK?
Hey, no! No.
Get out. Get out.
Hey! Find another cockpit,
Top Gun.
No. Get...
Let's just get in the back, OK?
Ha ha ha!
Ahem.
Guess who's back?
- Ugh.
Hey!
I'll meet you at the end.
Here! All right!
Cool!
Hey. How'd you guys
get in here?
What? I'm 55 inches.
- Sure. Come on out.
- Oh, man.
You, too. Out.
- Ready?
- Ohh!
I told you
we wouldn't get away with it.
You OK?
Let's go on the bumper cars.
Come on. Here we go.
Yeah!
What's up, man? I'm good.
Dare you to, uh, flash me
them sweet, sweet titties...
when we go through the loop.
All right. Ha ha!
Yo! What, you can't read?
Oh. Well, can I just put it
in my pocket, man?
- Is that cool?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Cool.
Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
Oh!
Aw, shit!
Here you go!
Whoo-ooh!
Whoo! Win, baby!
Yes, baby! Win!
Come on!
Come on. Get hyped.
The first hill's so high.
Yeah.
This is what we need!
- Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Let's do this!
- Just win!
Ow!
Whoo!
Aw, yeah!
Whoo! Shit!
Aah!
Oh, man.
Oh, my God!
Here we go!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Aah!
Yeah! Whoo!
- Aah!
Ha ha!
Aah! Aah! Ha ha ha!
Whoo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ha ha ha! Whoo!
- Whoo!
Aah! Aah!
Whoo!
Yeah! Show me your titties!
- Fuck off, Frankie!
- Oh!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Unh!
Oh, shit!
- Aah!
Aah!
Oh, my God!
We're gonna fall off!
Aah!
No!
- Aah!
- Aaah!
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Unh!
Oh!
- Yow!
- Kevin!
No!
Aah!
Whoa!
No! Aah!
Aah!
Erin, hang on!
Erin!
- Hang on!
- Don't let go!
I can't.
Aah!
No!
Oh, God!
Hang on, Wen.
Hang on! Help me rock it!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Unh!
Almost got it! Gently.
Aaaah!
No!
Unh! Aah!
Aah!
Yo. What, you can't read?
Oh, well. I'll just...
I'll put it in my pocket, OK?
Yeah.
Thanks, bro.
Ahh. All right.
Let's do this, Wen...
What're you...?
Here you go!
Yeah! Let's do it, baby! Whoo!
We have to get off of here.
No, don't push the button!
Don't! Don't push the button!
Unh! Let me off! Let me off!
Wen, Wen! It's all right.
Jesus, it's gonna be over...
No! It's gonna crash!
It's gonna crash!
Wendy?
The hydraulics will rupture!
The tracks'll collapse! Please!
- What's going on?
- Let me off!
Chick's on somethin'.
It's all right! You'll be OK!
OK, let 'em out. Just the back.
Wen. Hey! Wendy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax. Now, what's the matter?
I saw it. I saw it in my head.
The tracks collapsed.
The roller coaster crashed.
No, she was just a little upset before.
Man, please, can you please
control that bitch?
Damn. "It's gonna crash!
The hydraulics, the coaster!"
Man, she's just trying to get
some fuckin' attention.
You know what?
You're a real piece of shit, Lewis.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck moi?
No, man, fuck you!
Don't touch me.
Ow!
Hey, hey!
Unh!
Just relax!
Fight, man!
Hey. Hey. Let me out.
Nobody else gets off this ride!
Dude, let me off.
So high school.
Let's out.
- Calm down!
- Get off of him!
- Relax!
- lan!
Where you ladies going?
There's a fight.
Get him out of here!
Hey! Calm down! Relax!
Dude, let me off.
I gotta make sure she's OK.
- Relax! Calm down!
- # Hey! Ho! Let's go #
- Get your big ass off me, man!
- # Hey, ho, let's go! #
- Let me out!
Dude!
# Hey, ho, let's go,
hey, ho, let's go #
- Here we go!
- Let me off!
# Hey, ho #
Dude, that's my girlfriend!
Oh, my God!
Whoo!
Stop it! No! Stop it!
Stop it! Please!
Please, the tracks are broken.
Stop! Stop! Please!
Jason!
Hey, just relax, OK?
- Please!
- Ease up, man. She's all right.
OK? Just let her settle down.
She can settle down at home!
Now listen...
what is your home phone number?
OK, we're gonna call your mother.
Everything will be taken care of...
Aah!
Oh, my God! Jason!
Ohh.
Hey, Wendy!
Hey!
Wait! Wendy!
Hey! Hey, Wen. Wait.
I need... I need to talk to you
about something.
Just here to pick up my diploma.
You're not going to graduation?
No.
Look, you're not the only one
in a fucked up place, OK?
God, I mean,
I just thought maybe...
it'd be good for you to be somewhere
where other people feel the same way.
At graduation?
No. Thanks.
I've had enough funerals.
Then do it for J and Carrie.
Do what? If you die,
then there's nothing...
then you're just dead,
and they don't know.
And if they are up in Heaven
with Lincoln and Gandhi...
do you think they really care about
our high school graduation? No.
I am alive, and I don't care.
As soon as I pull out
of that parking lot...
I am so out of McKinley.
Without J, what's here for me?
I'm here. OK?
I made a promise to J
that I would take care of you.
On the ride. For 3 minutes.
You weren't making
the promise for a lifetime.
Kevin...
if it wasn't for
you and J being friends...
and me and Carrie being friends...
we wouldn't have even hung out.
We don't even like each other.
"lan McKinley."
How pathetic is it
that my last name...
is the same as my high school?
Julie, look who
I got to sign my yearbook.
- No way. Nice.
- Yeah.
I think we should invite her.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Wen? Um...
So we're ready
for graduation tonight...
we're going to
the tanning salon after this...
and we are so totally cool
if you wanna come with.
Totally.
And just like, talk if you want.
Here's my cell.
I already have your number.
That was so nice of us.
You're not alone.
God, I appreciate
everyone trying to help.
OK? I really do.
No, it's happened before.
OK? I went online looking for
an explanation about...
Wendy, just... just listen
to me, all right?
All right, look, I went online
looking for an explanation...
about what happened,
and I found out...
about this high school
French class from New York.
Six years ago
they went on a trip to Paris.
When they were boarding...
a kid had a vision that
the plane was gonna explode.
Just like you did.
He freaked out...
and seven people
got off the plane.
Just like us.
And on takeoff,
Flight 180 blew up.
And over the next several months...
everyone who got off that plane
started dying in weird accidents.
They died in the order they would've
if they had stayed on the plane.
Unless someone intervened,
then it skipped them.
Fuck you, Kevin.
W-Wendy! Wendy! Hey!
Ohh, every time we come here.
I was thinking of going
for 20 minutes in the Muller.
We did that for all the funerals
and it turned out amazing.
Yeah, but that was just
a couple of weeks ago, though.
I mean, we're still pretty bronzed.
I was just thinking
we could go for, like, a tune-up.
I just wanna make sure
that we look our best.
Yeah.
You know, for all those kids
that died that night...
who will never get a graduation.
You know what?
You're totally right.
- I'm sorry.
- Mmm.
This is my... my good guy
luck bracelet...
that Grandma left me in her will.
Ohh!
Julie?
I need...
I could use some help.
I have such...
such guilt over Jason.
I should never have let
that ride go.
God. I'm usually such
a control freak...
but I didn't do
enough to stop it.
I should've done everything
I could to stop it.
And I would give anything...
to have a second chance.
But I never can.
I don't want to some day
feel that way about you, Julie.
I mean,
I can't talk to Mom and Dad.
You're all I have left.
You think when I find a place...
maybe you could come stay
with me for a while?
You know I will.
You...
keep this now...
and I'll get it
when I come see you.
Oh. And... hey,
how 'bout on your end?
Can I use the school camera
for graduation tonight?
Yeah. As long as you bring it back
to school on Monday.
Done.
Oh. Um...
Actually, the battery is pretty low...
so why don't you go get ready,
and I'll recharge it a bit.
Cool.
In a hurry, Yuri.
Sorry, sorry.
Cell phone signal is shit in here.
I think tanning beds
mess with signal.
I must go outside.
Why don't you just use that phone?
I would, but she talks forever,
then my boss gives me shit.
Shit. That's her.
Ohh!
You know what? Just go outside.
We can deal with this ourselves.
OK.
Hey. No drinks in the room
this time, OK?
Good.
What are you doing?
Nobody is walking in here
and seein' me naked.
Oh, my God.
Dude, he said no drinks.
If you spill that shit...
we're gonna have to clean it
up like last time.
Mmm!
Happy, beyotch?
Nothing to spill.
Why does Yuri keep it
so cold in here?
Maybe it's supposed to be colder
for the machines or whatever.
Oh, a few degrees won't hurt.
Shit! I forgot my iPod.
Sucks, bitch.
They got CDs.
Ew. Celine?
Britney?
Dude, are we like the only cool people
that come here or what?
Uh, yeah.
Ugh. Whatever.
Why are you wearing underwear?
Steinmetz says
he gets off on tan lines.
All right.
# Roller coaster #
# Of love #
# Say what? #
# Roller coaster #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Right #
# Of love #
# Roller coaster #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Roller coaster of love #
# Roller coaster #
# Wow wow wow #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Roller coaster of love... #
# I #
# Huh, huh #
# I'm gonna ride, girl #
# Yeah #
# Whoo-hoo-hoo #
# Wow, yeah #
# Huh huh #
# Ow #
# Oh, oh #
Whoo.
# Roller coaster of love #
# Love roller coaster, girl #
# Roller coaster #
# Lovin' you
in a freaky world, child #
# Roller coaster of love #
Camera charged?
Oh, um, sorry,
the battery's totally dead.
Camera's not working. Sorry.
Look, Julie, I need a minute, OK?
Like private.
# That feels nice,
roller coaster #
# One more time #
# Roller coaster of love #
# Roller coaster #
Ugh.
It's way too warm in here now, huh?
I fucked up.
I set it too hot in here.
Huh?
Ow! Aah!
Hello?
- Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy...
- Psych! Leave a message.
Hi, Ashley, this is Wendy.
Gimme a call whenever
you guys are done.
Aah!
And thanks again for the invite.
- Someone help!
- Aah!
Sorry I was too late.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
Hey, open the door!
Help me!
Aah!
We may feel that our lives
are not our own.
That Death controls,
frames our lives.
Our birth's nothing
but death begun.
Yet, whether it is with
this tragic loss of young lives...
which we have
suffered much of late...
or with the soft passing
of the elderly in the night...
we are all equal in Death's eyes.
"Equal in Death's eyes?"
All of us?
How can you say that?
Shut up, McKinley.
Dude, think it through.
Charlie Manson made it to 70.
- Osama? Still kickin'.
- Let's go.
Pimps, vice-presidents
walking around.
- All the atrocities they've committed...
- Let's just go. Come on.
they're alive and well.
These two girls, who'd never
done shit to anybody...
- Shh!
- they don't get to make it to 18?
Where's the fucking
equality in that?
- What?
- Come on, man.
I can... Yeah. Fine.
Fine. All right. All right.
I'm fine. All right.
That's crazy.
Those of you who would like
to pay a final remembrance...
please step forward at this time.
I so feel this is so my fault.
How could it possibly be your fault?
Seein' women as nothin' but fun bags.
I mean... if I'd've seen their...
whatever... humanity...
they wouldn't have felt
the pressure to look so good.
Impress Franklin Cheeks.
Go on diets. Deodorize.
Stretch. Tan.
Don't be down, Frankie.
Be proud of your ability
to make everything...
that happens somehow
a story about you.
God!
Yo, man.
These things really suck, man.
Fucking boring.
Hey, if you ever have
to come to my funeral...
man, bring me a PSP or somethin'.
'Least I have somethin' to do then.
Whew.
Hello?
I'm with J.
What are you doing up here
in the nosebleeds?
You know, I could've
gotten you second row.
I didn't want to upset
anyone by being there.
And I wondered if
maybe here I could feel J's...
spirit or presence or...
whatever.
But now that I'm here...
if there's any place that makes me feel
like there's no life after death...
it's a cemetery.
Yeah, I haven't felt
Carrie's spirit either.
And I've tried.
Real hard. Heh.
I thought maybe
he's been with me since...
that night...
before I got on the ride...
Jason said...
God, and it was just
to get me on the ride...
he said...
"Your fear is from a sense
of having no control."
And I've felt that fear
since the moment he said it.
Even thought it maybe somehow
caused the hallucination...
but this fear is more
than just being scared.
It's like a presence.
Like a living thing
always with me.
You think it's J?
No, I know it's not.
This presence is the opposite
of how J made me feel.
It's cold and terrifying.
That's the last photograph
Lincoln posed for.
The photographic plate
was broken...
causing a line
that can't be removed.
Exactly where he was shot.
Look. See the shadow?
But what do these pictures
have to do with us?
Look. This occurred
one year to the day...
of the Flight 180 disaster.
Look at the road sign.
Look, I guess you came
to me with this...
because I'm responsible
for putting this in your head...
with the Flight 180 thing.
And it did happen,
and it may be occurring here...
but you can't believe
every weird thing out there...
because you're desperate
for an answer.
I took these.
That night.
These?
Are these it?
Oh, shit.
Oh... shit.
Ohh.
Whoa, whoa, hey.
You all right?
I'm feeling a little woozy.
When was the last time you ate?
I don't remember.
All right, come on. I'll drive.
OK, those kids on Flight 180
died in accidents...
in the order they would've died
if they'd have stayed on the plane.
OK?
So if this is that, then...
then Frankie was behind
Ashlyn and Ashley.
When I saw Ashley
and Ashlyn's picture...
I felt this instinct.
Like there was a hint
in the picture. I even...
I even called to see if
I could keep them from going.
Well, what's
Frankie's picture look like?
It's right here.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Wait! Watch out!
- Oh!
Hey! Hey! Are you crazy?
Sorry!
All right,
let's just eat over there.
And go through
the drive through.
I don't want anyone hearing
what we're talking about.
Well, it's nice to see
that things haven't made you...
any less of a control freak.
- You got it?
- Yeah, all right.
Here's Frank's picture.
All right.
Well, this is obvious.
He's falling off a ladder.
A rope ladder, though.
Maybe he might hang.
Look, or maybe it's not that literal.
All right, what's...
Could there be anything
in these prizes?
Oh, what, like he's gonna get
crushed by a giant Spongebob?
Hey, Spongebob lives underwater.
It's so sad that you know that.
All right. He won that tacky
mud-flap girl chain...
on this game, though, so...
aren't those usually
on those big 18 wheelers?
Yeah. Yeah.
God, I don't see it in
this picture anywhere though.
All right! God.
All right.
Uh, can I take your order?
Yeah. What do you want?
Are you OK?
Please tell me
there's a short in your wiring.
Whoa. Whoa. That guy's
way too close to my truck.
Hey, you're too fucking
close, man! Pull up!
Hey!
# There is someone #
Stop! Stop!
# Walking behind you #
Watch out! Shit!
- What the fuck?
- # Turn around #
- Oh, my God!
- # Look at me #
- Get out! Get out!
- What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
# Watching your footsteps #
Shit! Hey! Pull up, man!
Come on! Pull up!
- # Look at me #
- Unh! Shit!
- # There is someone #
- Back up!
Back up!
# Who really loves you #
# Here's my heart #
Watch your eyes!
Watch your eyes! Come here!
# In my hand #
# Turn around #
- # Look at me #
- Come on. Let's go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Unh!
- Oh!
- Unh!
We're all done here.
You need a ride?
Um, we can walk to my house...
and then I'll give you
a ride to yours.
No, thanks. We'll be OK.
Will we?
Yeah. We'll be all right.
I mean...
how Frank...
God, it... it's not only horrible...
but can you feel...
can you feel how vicious it was?
Easy.
OK? Easy.
Let's just...
let's just take a step back.
All right? He was behind
Ashley and Ashlyn on the ride...
but there was no ladder here.
You know, there was no rope.
Nothing in that picture pointed to this.
We were wrong about the photos.
I should've left town.
It's better not knowing.
No, it's never better
staying ignorant.
Willful ignorance
is surrendering control.
What, did you read that somewhere
in Mrs. Brooks' English class?
No. l... you know, I'm not...
I'm not the total idiot
you think I am.
OK, that's Lewis after Frank...
then lan and Erin.
There's a couple of kids behind them,
but I can't make them out...
because this guy's arm's
in the way. Can you?
No.
All right, you know what?
We'll ask Lewis, lan, and Erin
if they remember.
OK?
Are there any more pictures
from the roller coaster?
I guess...
that kind of thing
is gonna happen to us
for the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
You know, I was gonna...
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
Right after graduation.
Heh.
Oh.
No, wait.
Look, behind Stacy.
That's Frank.
This picture shows how he died.
All right, go back to Lewis.
OK, he's got that hammer.
And the weight looks like
it's coming down...
on his head.
No, no, no, check this out.
Right now Lewis is down at State
for football training camp.
State's team is called the Sultans.
That's it. That's the clue.
We have to tell him.
Show him these pictures.
Wouldn't you want to know?
Wait, there's pictures of us in there?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Huh. No.
No. I don't want to see mine.
No. Huh.
What about willful ignorance?
Well, I'm full of shit, all right?!
I mean, I never thought
I could see my own death...
before it happened, Wendy.
No, you know what?
We can tell Lewis, but...
Seriously, if there's any way
to beat this thing...
I gotta stay focused...
and if I look at that picture,
all I'm gonna do is obsess.
So, you know what?
No, I don't want to see it.
I mean, unless we have to.
You mean until we have to.
One more thing.
Is it bad?
I mean, is it, like,
painful or embarrassing?
I mean, there's nothing, like,
up my ass or anything, right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
You on crack. Both of you.
Just listen, OK?
Ashley and Ashlyn were first.
Then Frankie Cheeks
and then you. This is the...
- Aw, come on, Kevin.
- Listen.
McKinley and Erin
were next, all right?
And there were two people in front of us.
Do you remember who they were?
Fuck no, and I don't care.
And you shouldn't care either, man...
'cause what you're tellin' me
right now is straight bullshit.
Just listen, Lewis.
Kevin, it's like those stories.
Like this guy was killed
by a car he sold 10 years ago.
Two sisters, right, were killed when
they were driving to visit each other.
You know, shit like that, man.
Fuck the Bruins!
Oh, yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Bruin faggots!
Yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Man, you're reading into this shit
like them damn urban legends.
Three people have died, Lewis.
I mean, if you think
this can be written off...
as a simple coincidence
and it ends there...
you're in serious denial.
Unh! What about you two, huh?
What?
You both lost people real close
to you in a fucked-up way.
And in order to feel
less guilty or whatever...
seeing signs and patterns, man.
I don't blame you.
But it's wrong, dawg.
Unh! It's wrong.
That's denial.
Unh!
- Unh!
- You got it!
OK, what about what happened
at the roller coaster? Huh?
Wendy saw it.
Man, she got a hunch.
Fuckin' intense, but she got a hunch.
Man, I'm here because I get
good hunches before every down.
No, you know
they're either gonna run or pass.
Hers came to her from nowhere.
You're here and alive because of her.
No, I'm alive because of me.
No, listen.
You don't get it, man.
Does that make sense to you?
There's nothing to get, Kevin!
It's bullshit.
No, just hear me out, all right?
Unh.
# Yeah #
Talk about a vision.
Man, I seen my whole life played out...
and it sure as hell
ain't gonna end now. Unh!
It's going just as I saw it.
35 high school games
without an injury.
- USA Today All-American.
- Second team.
- Free ride to play for the Sultans!
- The Bruins passed on you.
Man, fuck the Bruins!
- Fuck 'em!
- You goddamn right!
What the fuck is a Bruin anyway?
Aah!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Four years from now...
Lewis Romero goin' in
the second round to Oakland.
Unh!
He's gonna romp and stomp.
15 seasons, with four Super Bowl
rings on his fingers.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Fuck Death!
Death is a fuckin' Denver fan.
Death wear blue and orange.
Real men wear black.
Lewis ain't afraid of no Death.
Death is afraid of me!
Death fears me!
Kevin.
'Cause, baby, I just win.
I just win, Kevin!
That's all I know how to do!
I just win! Unh!
Fuck Death!
- Fuck the Bruins!
- Yeah!
Aah!
- Look out!
- Lewis!
Man, that was close, Lewis.
Hey, did you see that?
Whoo! What I tell you,
Kevin, huh?
Fuck Death! I just win!
That's all I know
how to do, Kevin.
Baby, I just win!
Aaaaah!
- Ooooh!
- God!
Did I do something...
to bring this on everybody?
Don't, Wendy.
But why me?
All those people out there
wanting to have a premonition...
or see a ghost or whatever,
and I don't.
I just want it to stop.
Just stop.
I don't know why, Wendy...
but you didn't do anything.
All right? This is just...
I don't know. I mean,
I wish I knew why, you know?
I wish I could... I could
come up with a guess even...
to make you feel OK, but...
You know, I can't.
Yeah.
There's nothing I can do.
Can you drive?
Heh.
Yeah.
You know, by the way,
that... that picture of me.
My, uh, my head's not, like,
through the windshield or anything?
You know,
crushed by a steering wheel?
lmpaled by a gear shift?
Right?
Zip, it's Pip.
Have you cut
those plywood orders yet?
Uh, that's a big no, Pip.
Osama bin Supervisor wants me
to get rid of these pigeons first.
They keep settin' off the alarms.
Hello, babies.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, ha ha ha! Heh.
Hey. After I, uh, restock
this stuff...
that these pinhead customers
can't manage...
to return to the shelves
themselves...
we can blow out of here, OK?
Righty-o, babe.
Aah!
Erin, it's Wendy and Kevin.
Shit!
You scared the shit out of me!
Yeah, wait till you hear
what we have to tell you.
Zip, it's Pip. Come over here.
You are gonna trip
when you hear this.
Well, paint me intrigued, Pip.
I'm on my way.
So let me get this straight.
I'm gonna O.D. on nail polish...
and lan is gonna be
embarrassed to death?
You saw what happened
to Wendy, right?
What's happened to the others?
I mean, you just saw their pictures.
Oh, my God, guys,
what's going on?
What's going on?
That's crazy! That's crazy!
Ha ha!
We need to know who was sitting
behind you on the roller coaster.
OK, who was sitting behind us
on the roller coaster?
Oh! Oh, wait! Wasn't it
that one guy who got voted...
most likely to become
manager at Red Lobster?
Oh, no. You know what?
God, I remember.
There was this guy,
uh, black cloak...
I didn't see his face, but, um...
the ride attendant
did take his sickle...
before the ride started
if that's helpful in any way.
Do you think we care
if you laugh at us?
This is our lives, OK?
What choice do we have?
Just give into it?
Oh, God. You know what?
There is no "it."
OK, wait, are you guys saying
that Death is, like, a person?
No. It's like... like a force.
Yeah. Well, you know what?
A force is just a force.
It's nothing else.
Just transferred energy.
I mean, it has no goals,
no awareness that is a force.
But there is awareness, McKinley.
In fact, in past cases,
if the next in line is saved...
it'd skip that person.
That's why we're here.
Oh, man,
what have you been smoking?
Ha ha!
- Top shelf.
- OK.
Kevin! Those banners.
They're in the picture.
lan, watch those boxes!
What the fuck, man?
You said those boxes were falling!
No, I said watch the boxes.
Really? What for?
They're not doing anything.
We're not gonna apologize
for trying to save you.
You haven't seen or been through
what we have... yet.
Oh. Yet.
OK, so who's next in this theory
you have, me or lan?
Well, we know the order of how
we were sitting on the roller coaster...
but not how it works
with people who sat together.
OK, we don't know
if Ashley or Ashlyn died first.
Hmm. God, Death is
fucking complicated.
Ha ha!
No, you know what?
It's not complicated.
It's simple. People die.
That's just part of life.
150,000 people a day, actually.
You know? I mean...
we're biological entities,
and death is just...
- Top shelf.
- the end of biological function.
It's as simple as that.
How can you explain
what happened to us as simple?
I mean, if Wendy never had
that premonition...
and none of us had gotten off that ride,
we'd all be dead right now.
- Does that not make sense to you?
- Oh, yeah.
Kevin, how come when a guy dies
of a plain heart attack...
no one goes, like...
"Oh, wow, he was
eating French toast...
"when Princess Diana
died in Paris...
"and then he saw her funeral on TV,
and now he's dead"?
You know why?
Because they'd sound crazy...
so guess how you two
sound right now? Crazy.
Zip, I'm done.
So finish cutting those orders...
- so we can get out of here.
- OK!
Unh!
Heh heh!
Ugh!
Sick.
OK.
Let's go with
what you guys are saying.
Let's just say, you know...
that Death does have
a conscious plan...
and that it's been
set into motion. Great.
So, Newton's third law of motion,
and, well, look...
I'm just guessing
that it goes for Death, too...
when he's working in our world.
Newton says that every action
has an equal and opposite reaction.
So, that means that...
if Death has taken action,
so can we.
And that that action
we take might have...
an opposite reaction
that thwarts Death's intent.
You're being a fucker, but go on.
OK. OK.
What if, for example...
the last in line were to make
the utilitarian choice...
Kill themselves.
Wow! Wow! That's pretty much
gonna ruin any plan...
that Death's put in motion.
And even better...
hey, it's gonna save
five skipped lives.
Any takers?
Nah, I didn't think so.
There! Those!
Ugh!
Aah!
Ooh!
Unh! Unh!
Unh!
Aah!
I didn't say anything.
I mean, I think...
they were trying to scare us
into saying something...
but they had nothing
to keep me there.
What'd you tell 'em?
Everything.
I didn't do anything.
I told them about
the pictures in the camera...
and Flight 180
and Frankie and Lewis...
and why we went to see
lan and Erin and...
Did they believe you?
Yeah, right.
Would you believe me?
No, they looked at me
like I was crazy.
10 hours they had us in there.
For all we know...
whoever was sitting
behind Erin is already dead.
And we're next.
Now.
lan almost died first,
but we intervened.
So it skipped lan.
That's... that's how we regain control.
If someone intercedes...
the life that was supposed
to be next is skipped.
All right, wait, wait, wait.
So, going by the way we sat
on the roller coaster...
Well, I'm next... and then you.
We can beat this.
We're so close.
We can't give up.
All right, my dad's here.
He's gonna give me a ride back.
But are you sure
we shouldn't stick together?
It's just for a couple of hours.
All right? A couple of hours.
Go back, look at the pictures,
see if you can find any more clues...
and I'll ask everybody I see if they know
if anyone else got off the ride.
OK?
Was there something
I should know about going?
No, it's just...
I'll just be freaking out
every second...
hoping you're OK.
Why?
I mean,
we don't even like each other.
Heh.
Come here.
OK?
All right, I got my cell.
OK.
Hey, Wen?
So we're meeting some guys
at that centennial thing...
and I could really use
my good-luck... bracelet.
Mmm.
Huh.
Hey, this is Julie.
Leave a message.
Call me on my cell right away.
Hello?
Do you remember Julie
being on the roller coaster?
What, your sister? No.
No, she would've said
something by now.
The person sitting
behind lan and Erin...
was wearing the exact same
charm bracelet...
our grandmother gave her.
Amber or Perry
were probably with her...
so they're next.
I gotta find Julie.
She went to
the tricentennial thing.
Well, l... I'm here now,
working security.
I'll start looking for her.
- I'm on my way.
- Wen, wait.
Look, after them, we're next.
So in case somethin'
happens to 'em...
before we meet up...
remember that time
we talked about?
When to look at our pictures?
It's now.
Great. Mine has no clue.
It's just me standing in front of
a blank background...
with Jason at
the amusement park.
Wait. McKinley.
lan? Is he in the picture?
No, but it... it feels like a clue.
And yours is the picture
that I took...
when I flashed the camera
in your face.
It's all out of focus
and overexposed, like...
Like a firework
went off in my face?
# There is someone #
# Walking behind you #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Watching your footsteps #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Who really loves you #
The British are coming!
- Whoo!
- Yay!
Get 'em while they're hot!
Take it to those Redcoats!
Column, advance!
The kite is aloft.
Now, let us hope
for some lightning.
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
But he kept insisting.
"Get over here," right?
This is awesome, dude!
Heh heh.
Whoa. Hey!
Ha ha! Come on!
Hey, get out of here with those, man!
You're gonna set these off!
Hurry, dude.
Come on, man, let's go!
Hurry up!
Ladies and gentlemen,
to celebrate McKinley's tricentennial...
the fireworks extravaganza
will begin shortly.
Oh, my God. Julie.
- What?
- Look.
There's Kahlil.
Should we?
Hey, guys. I'm sorry,
but you can't be here, OK?
The viewing site is over there.
You too, sir. Come on.
They're not gonna
make us move, are they?
I don't fucking believe them.
- OK, we gotta clear out.
- Mm-hm.
Excuse me.
- Ladies.
- Boys.
What's going on?
Hey, Julie.
- You three need to come with me.
- What did we do?
Look, it's for your own safety,
Julie, all right?
I'll tell you about it as soon as
we get away from here, OK?
Let go of me!
Julie.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Julie!
Heh heh heh!
- Sweet.
- Ha ha!
Yeah!
Light it! Light it!
Go, go, go, man!
Julie!
Uh! Oh!
- Oh, shit!
- Dude, we gotta bail!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Unh! Hey!
Julie! No, wait, wait.
You're in danger, OK?
I'm trying to explain something.
Let me explain this to you.
Julie, look out!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Aah!
Julie!
Unh!
Aah! Unh!
Cut him off!
Unh!
Aah!
OK, OK.
Stay back! He's dangerous!
I got him.
- Just let me go.
- No, Julie.
You have to tell me,
you have to listen.
Tell me who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Oh, my God,
Julie, are you all right?
Listen to me!
You have to tell me...
who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Who? She's next!
Aah!
Kevin.
Fire!
You saved my life.
Thanks for that, McKinley.
- Shut up, McKinley!
- No!
We have to get out of here now.
What's the deal?
lan McKinley.
He causes my death.
In my picture I was wearing
the McKinley grad night shirt.
- He's the clue.
- What?
There's a first aid tent,
there should be security.
Get the fuck outta here, McKinley!
Hey, I'm just celebrating
our town's tricentennial.
You followed me!
Oh! You are paranoid.
But, hey, I saw what happened.
You're next, right?
You're the end of it, aren't you?
Man, I would be paranoid, too.
You didn't even believe me!
Yeah, well, seeing is believing.
Then you have
to stay away from me!
"Have to"?
Wow, that's extreme.
Oh, no way.
Do I cause your death?
Just like you caused Erin's?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, what? What?
You have a vision? Was I in it?
Was I in a picture?
Just tell me how to start it off!
Let's get this over with!
You'll save me
if you just stay away!
Then it'll all be over!
What do I care? It skipped me.
For me, it is over.
I'm not dying.
I'm not dying!
Ha ha ha!
You see?
I'm not gonna die!
It's you, Wendy! You're dead!
# Came back down
from this fight #
- Hi!
- # Will get ya deeper #
# And make you right #
Thank you.
# Bruno's drops
threaten her... #
Wait, what about
that great curry place?
Don't we get off at Booth?
Oh, you mean Gupta's.
You get off at Oswald.
Oh, that's right.
You know, if I can't be home
for Thanksgiving...
I need some semblance
of a traditional dinner.
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
If you don't have turkey
for one Thanksgiving...
is that really gonna kill you?
# There is someone #
# Walking behind you #
# Turn around #
# Look at me #
# There is someone #
# Watching your footsteps #
# Turn around #
# There is someone #
# Who really needs you #
# Here's my heart #
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
This is Booth Street.
Next stop is Oswald.
End of the line.
The next stop
is the end of the line.
Wendy! Next stop after this.
- Let's just walk.
- It's freezing out.
Yeah, but the air'll feel good.
I could use some air.
Yeah!
Ha ha ha! Yeah, man!
All right, man. See ya.
Let's go, Bruins!
Bruins, yeah!
Hey, man, peace out!
- Come on.
- Excuse me.
- Watch out!
- Hey, Bruins!
You missed the beginning.
Did you see that?
This is it!
Yo, comin' through. Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this. Here.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
I thought you weren't
coming till tonight.
Well, Dad's car just, like,
dies out of nowhere...
and he couldn't get it fixed
anywhere on a holiday...
so instead of sitting around
for a few hours...
I lucked out and caught
an early train.
I hope I'm not messing you up or...
No, no, it's just, um...
I think I had a sense
that you were coming now.
I was just...
I was feeling like I did that night.
No. No, it's over.
You, me, Kevin went over
a thousand scenarios.
lan was gonna cause your death...
you intervened,
and it skipped us.
Look, I'm not worried.
I ran into Kevin at home.
He's not worried.
And, if I were you...
until something happens
to me and then Kevin...
you've got nothing
to worry about.
You're right.
Uhh.
Hey, l... I want you to meet
my roommate and my friend, OK?
Yeah.
Hey, guys. This is Julie, my...
What are you doing here?
Wendy! Julie!
What are the chances?
How long have you been
on this train?
Uh, since home.
I was headin' up
to check out the game.
I was gonna look you up
afterwards.
You OK?
Is something wrong?
Aah!
- Aah!
- Unh!
- Julie, stay down!
- Aah!
Julie!
Aah!
- Kevin!
- Unh!
Aaaaaah!
Oh, God!
Aah!
Aah! Unh!
No!
I was gonna look you up
afterwards, but...
You OK?
Is somethin' wrong?
The train...
Oh, shit. Not again.
We gotta get out!
It's not working.
Somebody stop the train!
ViSTA™ vista.vnhd@gmail.com